[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these Australian reptiles is the largest living crocodile in the world?", "correct_answer": "The saltwater crocodile", "incorrect_answers": ["The thorny devil", "The weedy sea dragon", "The blue-tongued skink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chefs James Beard and Julia Child were lifelong friends.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of Santa Klaus reindeers\u2019 name means lightning?", "correct_answer": "Blitzen", "incorrect_answers": ["Dasher", "Prancer", "Donner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The horror/comedy movie The Toxic Avenger was produced by Troma Studios.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the middle name of American fashion designer Calvin Klein?", "correct_answer": "Richard", "incorrect_answers": ["Theodore", "Abraham", "William"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many law enforcement officers were killed at the motel in Northern California in the movie Eve of Destruction?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["7", "1", "11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This planet is has the largest  group of moons - 31, but it is best known for its ring system.", "correct_answer": "Saturn", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Mars", "Venus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest island in the Mediterranean Sea, famous for one of the worlds most active volcanoes - Etna.", "correct_answer": "Sicily", "incorrect_answers": ["Crete", "Sardinia", "Corse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An icon or animation to represent a participant used in Internet chat and games is referred to as this.", "correct_answer": "Avatar", "incorrect_answers": ["Bitmap", "Cookie", "Applet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is the popular Japanese meal Karaage prepared?", "correct_answer": "By deep frying", "incorrect_answers": ["By roasting", "By stewing", "By boiling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is a Yin Sign associated with the Wood Element, that some people like as a pet.  The sign before it can be fierce and the sign which follows it can fly.", "correct_answer": "Rabbit", "incorrect_answers": ["Monkey", "Goat", "Dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The distance between the Moon and the Earth is approximately this much.", "correct_answer": "238,897 miles (384,467km)", "incorrect_answers": ["62,000 miles (100,000km)", "155,342 miles (250,000 km)", "260,975 miles (420,000 km)"]}]